http://counselingtoys.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

About Us
Welcome to our Store!
I founded Counselingtoys.com in 2007 after discovering a need for a true Non-directive Play Therapy and Sandtray supply store.
Children need specific toys to act out themes during Play Therapy.
This often requires hard to find “old fashioned” toys that engage the child.
One day it dawned on me how much time I'd spent gathering my collection of Play Therapy toys and Sandtray miniatures.
I knew busy therapists didn't have time to search for these items, and so Counselingtoys.com was born.
Counselingtoys.com set the precedent for most Play Therapy Kits and Sandtray Kits in existence today.
We are now the global leader for Non-Directive Play Therapy and Sandtray supplies.
Our kits are designed by credentialed professionals for credentialed professionals.
Each and every toy and miniature has a unique purpose.
Unlike others, we're not randomly boxing toys or copying others' work.
We believe our integrity and devotion to our customers is unprecedented.
Please drop us a line or two if you have any questions about our products, Sandtray or Play Therapy.
We'd love to hear from you.
Shipping
Most domestic orders are delivered within 7 business days.
Please let us know if you need it sooner.
Sometimes we can offer an in-house rush for no additional cost.
2nd day and next day air is also available.
International orders - please see the shipping and returns page for more info.
Shop with Confidence
Your privacy and security is very important to us.
Sensitive data (such as credit card numbers) is protected with the highest level of 256-bit encryption. Credit card information is not stored or available to anyone other than the processing bank.
Access to other personal information is restricted both online and offline.
Shopping Cart - 0 item(s) - $0.00
Log In
Shop
Play Therapy Kits
Sand Tray Therapy Kits
Sand Tray Miniatures
Aggressive/Power Toys
Art Toys
Categories
Play Therapy KitsSand Tray Therapy KitsSand Tray MiniaturesAggressive/Power ToysArt ToysFidget ToysPlay Therapy AccessoriesPlay Therapy BooksPlay Therapy GamesRole PlayGift CertificatesClearanceSpecials ...Featured Products ...All Products ...
Information
About Us
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Contact Us
Site Map
Gift Certificate FAQ
Discount Coupons
Newsletter Unsubscribe
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Counselingtoys.com values your privacy.
We strive to make sure your experience with us is as safe and fulfilling as possible.
We have established the following privacy policy to explain how your information is used.
We use Google Analytics to gather non-personally identifiable information about how visitors utilize our website.
This tool uses cookies to gather data about how visitors utilize our website.
We analyze this information to find better was to make the site perform better for our customers.
You may opt out of Google Analytics by clicking here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
Personal information such as name and address is only gathered when you voluntarily submit it to us
through web forms, emails, etc.
Your private information will not be sold, rented, leased, or disclosed in any manner to any third party without your prior consent, unless otherwise required by law, or except as may be necessary for the performance of CounselingToys.com, for auditing requirements, or as part of regulatory compliance. CounselingToys.com reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time. Be sure to check this page periodically for updates. CounselingToys.com Privacy Statement Copyright © 2009 by CounselingToys.com. All rights reserved.
Quick LinksHomeFeatured ProductsSpecialsWhat's NewAll Products ...
InformationAbout UsSite MapGift Certificate FAQDiscount CouponsNewsletter Unsubscribe
Customer ServiceContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseMy Account
Important Links Play Therapy Room Set Up
Follow Us
Copyright © 2020 Counselingtoys.com
